[
    {"question":"A","ans":"ア"},
    {"question":"I","ans":"イ"},
    {"question":"U","ans":"ウ"},
    {"question":"E","ans":"エ"},
    {"question":"O","ans":"オ"},
    {"question":"KA","ans":"カ"},
    {"question":"KI","ans":"キ"},
    {"question":"KU","ans":"ク"},
    {"question":"KE","ans":"ケ"},
    {"question":"KO","ans":"コ"},
    {"question":"SA","ans":"サ"},
    {"question":"SHI","ans":"シ"},
    {"question":"SU","ans":"ス"},
    {"question":"SE","ans":"セ"},
    {"question":"SO","ans":"ソ"},
    {"question":"TA","ans":"タ"},
    {"question":"CHI","ans":"チ"},
    {"question":"TU","ans":"ツ"},
    {"question":"TE","ans":"テ"},
    {"question":"TO","ans":"ト"},
    {"question":"NA","ans":"ナ"},
    {"question":"NI","ans":"ニ"},
    {"question":"NU","ans":"ヌ"},
    {"question":"NE","ans":"ネ"},
    {"question":"NO","ans":"ノ"},
    {"question":"HA","ans":"ハ"},
    {"question":"HI","ans":"ヒ"},
    {"question":"FU","ans":"フ"},
    {"question":"HE","ans":"ヘ"},
    {"question":"HO","ans":"ホ"},
    {"question":"MA","ans":"マ"},
    {"question":"MI","ans":"ミ"},
    {"question":"MU","ans":"ム"},
    {"question":"ME","ans":"メ"},
    {"question":"MO","ans":"モ"},
    {"question":"YA","ans":"ヤ"},
    {"question":"YU","ans":"ユ"},
    {"question":"YO","ans":"ヨ"},
    {"question":"RA","ans":"ラ"},
    {"question":"RI","ans":"リ"},
    {"question":"RU","ans":"ル"},
    {"question":"RE","ans":"レ"},
    {"question":"RO","ans":"ロ"},
    {"question":"WA","ans":"ワ"},
    {"question":"WO","ans":"ヲ"},
    {"question":"GA","ans":"ガ"},
    {"question":"GI","ans":"ギ"},
    {"question":"GU","ans":"グ"},
    {"question":"GE","ans":"ゲ"},
    {"question":"GO","ans":"ゴ"},
    {"question":"ZA","ans":"ザ"},
    {"question":"JI","ans":"ジ"},
    {"question":"ZU","ans":"ズ"},
    {"question":"ZE","ans":"ゼ"},
    {"question":"ZO","ans":"ゾ"},
    {"question":"dA","ans":"ダ"},
    {"question":"JI","ans":"ヂ"},
    {"question":"ZU","ans":"ヅ"},
    {"question":"dE","ans":"デ"},
    {"question":"dO","ans":"ド"},
    {"question":"BA","ans":"バ"},
    {"question":"BI","ans":"ビ"},
    {"question":"BU","ans":"ブ"},
    {"question":"BE","ans":"ベ"},
    {"question":"BO","ans":"ボ"},
    {"question":"PA","ans":"パ"},
    {"question":"PI","ans":"ピ"},
    {"question":"PU","ans":"プ"},
    {"question":"PE","ans":"ペ"},
    {"question":"PO","ans":"ポ"},
    {"question":"N","ans":"ン"}
    
]